Hello nowadays video to America
motorcycle insurance online secondary
bike par motorcycle and insurance kata
yono ami sadharan hota dutipotal behavior
kudi policybazaar kumba lovers duty
potli astrology bear so today what ami
policybazaar total the ki kor dcha kar
insurance kat khe setup doosra karan
insurance khata general
policybazaar
look at you wheeler insurance ko laptop
me humne gaadi kisi number food
gaadi number
basic key details
insurance
company
basic details
looking you without GST no GST one
Hindu and one you variable plan
amount 664 seater is given
limited third party i just police
murder speech which they ke insurance
katye rakhna ki season me yehi plan tha
select continue to
vehicle option is click
policy insurance company automatic
registration
debit card number
KYC verification code number and date of
birth is complete KYC option is
click karo verification ne
such KYC verification field hello
document
upload
policy you KYC upload from inside the biology number
complete KYC verification
document upload then identity procedure
pan card  While selecting
and the questions will be that Aadhar card was necessary,
see, I am saying that
PAN card photo and Aadhar card are
in front,
Aadhar card number
document has been uploaded, the
policy is
giving complete vehicle details, it has the policy icon
and it has not been issued at all, see
what was the problem, I have seen it, so thank you, if you have
said while uploading then show me the
pair, the policy will be issued within an hour, so the
mail ID which was given is the mail
ID, give the mail ID in the check code, the policy will be issued
by the policy soft copy, that
party has been given, see which movement is behind,
refresh after coming to Nami,
but I am not the policy which has been issued,
check the mail from here, see congratulations from the message